Guide to the Washington Irving Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Printed Material, 1850-1882; Series IV; 0.83; (2 boxes)
  - Extra-illustrations in Irvingiana: A Memorial of Washington Irving, circa 1860 (Box 23)
  - Extra-illustrations in Irvingiana: Homes & Haunts of Washington Irving, undated; 10 (Box 23)
  - Portrait of Washington Irving, mezzotint, undated
  - Title pages for Irving books published by G. P. Putnam, circa 1882 (Box 24)
  - "Washington Irving and His Friends," engraving, 1864 (Box 24)
  - Engravings of Sunnyside and Old Dutch Church, Sleepy Hollow by Rockwood & Company, 1868 (Box 24)
  - Engravings of "An Indian Village of the Manhattans", undated (Box 24)
  - "Sunlight photograph from life" of unidentified building with a man in the foreground, undated (Box 24)
  - Illustrations for The Beauties of Washington Irving and Knickerbocker's History of New York based on drawings by George Cruikshank and published by William Tegg, undated (Box 24)
  - Illustrations for D. T. Valentine's Manual of the Corporation of the City of New York, undated (Box 24)
  - Illustrations for A History of New York from the Beginning of the World to the End of the Dutch Dynasty and other titles, circa 1850 (Box 24)
  - Photographs and illustrations of Spain, undated (Box 24)
- Oversize, 0.08; (1 box)
  - Portrait of Washington Irving, mezzotint, undated (Box 25)